All right, today's Big Up goes to white rappers?
Not plural, McLemore.
Okay.
He recently dropped a new song called Hins Hall
in reference to Columbia University's Hamilton Hall,
which pro-Palestine protesters renamed,
paying tribute to Hind Rajab,
a six-year-old Palestinian girl who,
along with her family and the EMTs who tried to save her,
were killed by Israeli tanks.
The song supports protesters at college campuses
calling for an end to Israel's war in Chesa.
It got me thinking, while people have been,
like, they've been on my head,
like, dang, how you don't care about Kendrick and Drake?
Ain't you a hip-hop head?
Like, you falling off, ma.
It just made me think, like,
where are the major Black artists with huge platforms
who are putting energy into important causes?
Today's letdown goes to the milkman.
So, Rachel Bailey had forgotten her breast pump
while on a couple's cruise,
which left her painfully engorged.
She was scared about getting an infection.
So her husband, Alexander, said,
hold my drink,
and decided to instead drink the milk from her breast.
He developed quite the palate for his wife's milk
because the feeding continued.
Wow.
So much so that she started to breastfeed him
at breakfast.
Wow.
Lunch.
And dinner.
You might have guessed it.
This couple is definitely from?
Florida.
That is correct.
But I'll bet you didn't guess
that they are Black people.
You lying.
Mm.
We are.